Well, I got to run.
The panel's tomorrow morning.
It's called, "Remembering Snow:
A Look Back."
(Bernadette:)I'll try to catch it.
(Glenn:)Oh, great.
(Glenn:)Bye.
Bye.
(Howard:)Hey... Bernie?
(Bernadette:)Yeah?
(Howard:)Please tell me he's
your gay cousin.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Bernadette:)He was one of my professors
in college.
(Howard:)Oh! That's a relief.
(Bernadette:)Then we went out
for a year.
(Bernadette:)Come on, let's check in,
so we can take that nap.
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)No, it's not necessarily
proportional...
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)Shut up!
(Howard:)That green bag
is Dr. Cooper's.
(Howard:)Here's an extra five.
Make him wait.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Howard:)Right to the nap, huh? Okay.